Many things
هناك الكثير من الأمور
people actually know are wrong.
التي يعرف الجميع في الواقع أنها خاطئة
They just deliberately choose to ignore them.
لكنهم يتجاهلونها عمدًا بشكل انتقائي
I believe this world
أنا أؤمن أن هذا العالم
still has a distinction between right and wrong, good and evil.
لا يزال فيه تمييز بين الصواب والخطأ، والخير والشر
The ultimate karma
وأن السبب والنتيجة
will eventually come back to oneself.
ستعود في النهاية إلى الشخص نفسه
So if I know the truth,
لذلك إذا عرفت الحقيقة
I can't ignore it.
فلا يمكنني تجاهلها
From Qi University?
إنه من جامعة تشي
You're my junior!
إنه زميلي الأصغر
Hello, senior.
مرحبًا أيها الزميل الأكبر
Come join my department.
تعال إلى قسمي
Isn't it Qi University tradition for seniors to look after juniors?
أليست رعاية الزملاء الأكبر للزملاء الأصغر تقليدًا في جامعة تشي؟
Kang, you wanted to see me?
الأخ كانغ، هل طلبتني؟
Take him to meet everyone in the department.
خذيه للتعرف على القسم
This is my assistant.
هذه مساعدتي
If you have any questions in the future, you can ask her.
يمكنك أن تسألها عن أي شيء لا تفهمه في المستقبل
Pursue excellence.
السعي للتميز
Embrace all rivers.
استيعاب كل الأنهار
The new store opened,
افتتاح المتجر الجديد
and then people in the kitchen got cross-infected with the flu.
ثم أصيب بعض الأشخاص في المطبخ بعدوى الإنفلونزا
They're now in the emergency room getting treatment.
وهم الآن في غرفة الطوارئ يتلقون العلاج
We're opening for business in an hour,
سنفتح المتجر للعمل بعد ساعة واحدة فقط
and we promised to make
لقد وعدنا اليوم بتقديم
100 free breakfasts today.
مائة وجبة إفطار مجانية
And you're only telling me about this problem now?
والآن فقط تخبرني أن هناك مشكلة؟
Just a moment.
انتظر لحظة
Here's your meal. Thank you.
تفضل طعامك، شكرًا
Thanks. Please leave us a good review.
شكرًا، لا تنس التقييم الإيجابي
OK. Hello.
حسنًا، مرحبًا
- Is everything free? - Yes.
هل كلها مجانية؟ نعم
Then I'd like one...
إذن أريد واحدة...
Ming.
آ مينغ
Go check it first.
اذهب وتحقق أولًا
- OK. - Outside.
حسنًا، في الخارج
- Good. - Right.
حسنًا، نعم
Has anyone not ordered yet?
هل هناك أحد لم يطلب بعد؟
- Can we order that... - That...
هل يمكننا طلب ذلك، ذلك
Can I order that latte?
هل يمكنني طلب ذلك اللاتيه؟
Yes.
نعم
Five blueberry croissants,
خمس كرواسون بالتوت الأزرق
and refill the soy milk.
وأضف حليب الصويا ذلك
If it's good, please leave a positive review.
إذا كان لذيذًا، فلا تنس التقييم الإيجابي
Ming, go check
آ مينغ، اذهب وتحقق بعد قليل
- if anyone hasn't ordered yet. - OK.
هل هناك من لم يطلب بعد؟ حسنًا
Keep things orderly.
نظم الترتيب قليلًا
Junyi, are the crispy fries ready?
هل البطاطس المقرمشة جاهزة يا جون يي؟
The 30th anniversary event.
فعالية الذكرى السنوية الثلاثين
The case about giving away toys with meal purchases.
إنها قضية شراء وجبة والحصول على لعبة مجانية
Today's bid scores are out.
لقد ظهرت درجات العروض التقديمية اليوم
But...
ولكن
Kang.
الأخ كانغ
This vendor is very familiar with our family.
هذا المصنع على علاقة وثيقة بعائلتنا
The owner is my father's friend.
المدير صديق والدي
This is the best one, right?
هذا هو الأفضل، أليس كذلك؟
It was chosen by the selection committee.
اختارته لجنة التقييم
Then there's nothing to worry about.
إذن ليس هناك ما يدعو للقلق
The toy factory matter is simple.
أمر مصنع الألعاب بسيط
First, help me think about
ساعدني في التفكير أولًا
the temporary difference I mentioned to you last time.
ذلك الفرق المؤقت الذي ذكرته لك في المرة الماضية
How to bring this sub-brand to Japan.
كيف نجعل هذه العلامة التجارية الفرعية تدخل اليابان
I told my father about it,
تحدثت مع والدي
and he immediately rejected it.
ورفض الفكرة على الفور
Help me figure out how to convince him.
ساعدني في التفكير بكيفية إقناعه
Chairman, excuse me.
سيدي الرئيس، عذرًا
May I have a moment?
هل يمكنني مقاطعتك للحظة؟
I wonder if you remember
لا أعرف إذا كنت لا تزال تتذكر
the temporary assignment case.
مشروع لينشي تشا
I've already rejected it.
لقد رفضته بالفعل
Chairman,
سيدي الرئيس
the VP probably hasn't had time
نائب المدير العام ربما لم يتمكن بعد
to show you these materials.
من إطلاعك على هذه الأشياء
Since everyone has no objections
بما أن الجميع ليس لديهم
to this temporary assignment plan,
أي اعتراض على مشروع لينشي تشا
let's proceed with implementation.
فلنبدأ بتنفيذه إذًا
I'll get ready right away.
سأستعد بسرعة
I'll make sure the Japanese
سأجعل اليابانيين
eat our breakfast every day.
يأتون لتناول فطورنا كل يوم
We don't need you for the expansion.
لن نحتاج إليك في توسيع أعمالنا
Jiang Zhihao,
جيانغ تشي هاو
you'll go to Japan.
أنت ستذهب إلى اليابان
But the temporary assignment case
لكن مشروع لينشي تشا
was proposed by the VP.
اقترحه نائب المدير العام
But you were the one who convinced me.
لكنك أنت من أقنعني به
Let me see your execution ability,
دعني أرى قدرتك على التنفيذ
if it's as strong as you claim.
وما إذا كانت قوية كما تدعي
Dad, expanding into the Japanese market
أبي، فتح السوق في اليابان
is a very important matter.
أمر مهم جدًا
You have other things to take care of.
لديك أمور أخرى لتنشغل بها
Fine.
حسنًا
Shall we now discuss
هل علينا الآن مناقشة
the autumn special menu?
قائمة الطعام الخاصة بالخريف
After getting the LinLin Breakfast Shop order,
بعد الحصول على طلبية من مطعم لينلين للفطور
I won't have to worry about money anymore.
لن أقلق بشأن المال بعد الآن
Kang said
قال الأخ كانغ
as long as you do a good job,
طالما أنجزت المهمة بشكل جيد
you'll get what you deserve.
فلن تحرم مما تستحقه
Your father bribed
والدك قدم رشوة
to help Lin Guangsheng's factory win the bid.
لتمكين مصنع لين غوانغ شنغ من الفوز بالعطاء
This kind of under-the-table dealing
هذا النوع من التعاملات السرية
almost caused LinLin Breakfast
كاد أن يضر بمطعم لينلين للفطور
to be associated with heavy metals.
بالارتباط بالمعادن الثقيلة
We're selling breakfast,
نحن نبيع وجبات الفطور
the source of daily energy.
مصدر الطاقة للنهار كله
You've damaged our company's image.
لقد تسببت بالإضرار بسمعة الشركة
Do you think you still deserve to stay?
هل تعتقد أنك لا تزال مؤهلًا للبقاء؟
Kang,
الأخ كانغ
what do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
You should leave.
عليك أن ترحل
Didn't you say to text me for important matters
ألم تقل أن ترسل رسالة نصية إذا كان هناك أمر مهم
instead of video calling?
وألا تتصل بمكالمة فيديو
I've been so worried these days
كنت قلقة عليك خلال الأيام الماضية
and you won't tell me anything when I ask.
وعندما أسألك لا تخبرني شيئًا
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير
You don't need to worry.
لا داعي للقلق
I've already taken care of his family.
لقد رتبت أمر عائلته
They won't trace anything here.
لن يتمكنوا من التحقيق هنا
I just can't help but worry.
لكنني أشعر بالقلق دائمًا
Focus on your studies there.
ركزي على دراستك هناك
I've got everything under control here.
أنا موجود هنا
Don't worry, okay?
لا تقلقي، مفهوم
Aren't you going on a business trip soon?
ألست مسافرًا في رحلة عمل قريبًا
Is everything prepared?
هل جهزت كل شيء
You're a student now,
أنتِ طالبة الآن
not my secretary.
ولستِ سكرتيرتي
I just told you and you've already forgotten.
لقد نسيتِ ما قلته للتو
Fine.
حسنًا
Go ahead and get ready then.
اذهب وجهز نفسك
I won't bother you anymore.
لن أزعجك بعد الآن
Bye.
وداعًا
Bye-bye.
مع السلامة
Everything is ready outside.
كل شيء جاهز في الخارج
Is it OK?
حسنًا
All good?
هل كل شيء على ما يرام
Not really.
ليس صحيحًا
What's wrong?
ما بك
Still nervous?
هل ما زلت متوترًا
No, not at all.
لا أبدًا
You've arranged everything for me.
لقد رتبتِ كل شيء لي
What would I be nervous about?
فلماذا أشعر بالتوتر
Don't worry.
اطمئن
The media reporters coming today
الصحفيون الذين سيأتون اليوم
are all acquaintances of my mother.
كلهم معارف والدتي
They won't ask you any tough questions.
لن يطرحوا عليك أسئلة صعبة
The coverage will definitely be positive.
وستكون التقارير إيجابية بالتأكيد
Let's go.
هيا
Regarding this incident,
بخصوص هذه الحادثة
we are truly sorry.
نحن نعتذر بشدة
In a moment, our Vice President
وسنطلب من نائب المدير العام بعد قليل
will provide further explanation.
أن يشرح للجميع
This time, LinLin
هذه المرة لين لين
used an unscrupulous chicken supplier,
استخدمت مورد دجاج غير موثوق
disappointing our customers
مما خيّب أمل
who have supported LinLin Breakfast for so long.
العملاء الذين دعموا فطور لين لين لفترة طويلة
We have already removed
لقد سحبنا
all problematic products.
جميع المنتجات المشكوك فيها
Today,
واليوم
we also have a new initiative
لدينا خطة جديدة
that we'd like to share with everyone.
نود مشاركتها معكم
Here we have excellent local farmers.
هؤلاء هم مزارعون محليون متميزون
We will use the highest quality ingredients
سنستخدم أفضل المكونات
to provide brand new products.
لتقديم منتجات جديدة تمامًا
For every purchase made by consumers,
وسنتبرع بخمسة بالمئة
we will donate 5% to charity
من كل عملية شراء للأعمال الخيرية
to give back to society.
لرد الجميل للمجتمع
Regarding the supplier issue,
بخصوص مشكلة المورد هذه المرة
and the oversights that occurred,
والأخطاء التي حدثت
we have conducted an internal review.
أجرينا مراجعة داخلية
We will launch a small farm initiative to give back to society.
سنطلق مشروع المزارعين الصغار لرد الجميل للمجتمع
We'll continue to support local agricultural products.
سنواصل دعم المنتجات الزراعية المحلية
Basically not a single word was changed.
لم يغير حرفًا واحدًا أساسًا
That's too much.
هذا مبالغ فيه جدًا
However,
ولكن
he actually spoke
في الواقع كان حديثه
pretty well.
جيدًا إلى حد ما
You should talk to your brother when you get a chance.
تحدث مع أخيك عندما تتاح لك الفرصة
Fashion is important.
الملابس مهمة جدًا
He dresses like a driver.
يرتدي ملابس كأنه سائق
It looks terrible.
يبدو قبيحًا جدًا
Xie Jinghan is here too.
شيه جينغ هان موجودة أيضًا
Xie Jinghan has been with the company for a long time.
شيه جينغ هان تعمل في الشركة منذ فترة طويلة
Yes, that's right.
نعم
Let me ask you something.
أريد أن أسألك
Your brother's former secretary, Li Peizhen,
سكرتيرة أخيك السابقة لي بي تشن
do you remember her?
هل تتذكرها
Peizhen?
بي تشن
Of course I remember.
نعم أتذكرها
The pretty one, right?
تلك الجميلة
What about her?
ماذا
Between those two,
من بينهما
who's more important to your brother?
من الأكثر أهمية لأخيك
Peizhen and Jinghan?
بي تشن وجينغ هان
I think Peizhen is more my brother's type.
أعتقد أن بي تشن هي النوع المفضل لأخي
You're good at sports.
أنت تلعب الكرة بشكل جيد
Do you know how to take photos?
هل تعرف كيف تلتقط الصور
I asked you to help me ask again but you won't.
طلبت منك أن تسأل مرة أخرى ولم تفعل
Don't you know that wedding venue owner?
ألست تعرف صاحب قاعة الزفاف؟
No, I've already asked.
لا، لقد سألت بالفعل
There's nothing. There's simply nothing.
لا يوجد شيء، لا يوجد
Are you holding a grudge?
هل تحمل ضغينة؟
Because I didn't invite you to my wedding?
لأنني لم أدعك لحضور حفل زفافي
So you won't help me?
ولذلك لا تريد مساعدتي
No, even if you invited me,
لا، حتى لو دعوتموني
I still wouldn't know who that person is.
لا أعرف من هو ذلك الشخص
You could check the security footage.
يمكنك مشاهدة تسجيلات كاميرات المراقبة
You're the neighborhood chief.
أنت رئيس الحي
No, I've already...
لا، لقد
Excuse me, please.
اسمحي لي بالمرور
Stop making a fuss.
توقفي عن هذا
I have a calligraphy class later.
لدي درس خط بعد قليل
Lin Liying.
لين لي يينغ
Can you please help me, Chief?
هل يمكنك المساعدة يا رئيس الحي؟
I voted for you last time.
لقد صوّتت لك في المرة الماضية
Fine, then vote for me next time.
حسنًا، صوتي لي في المرة القادمة
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
What exactly do you want?
ماذا تريدين بالضبط؟
Ding Huowang.
دينغ هوو وانغ
We've known each other for so many years.
نحن نعرف بعضنا منذ سنوات
Can't you be more helpful?
ألا يمكنك أن تكون أكثر فعالية في عملك؟
Ding is actually not bad.
آه دينغ ليس سيئًا في الواقع
He became the neighborhood chief at such a young age.
أصبح رئيس الحي وهو في سن صغيرة
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
He's quite handsome too.
وهو وسيم أيضًا
Gentle and caring, isn't he?
لطيف ويعتني بالآخرين، أليس كذلك؟
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
You're the crazy one.
أنتِ المجنونة
You say you only depended on Xiao Qian,
تقولين بفمك أنك فقط تعتمدين على شياو تشيان
and didn't actually like him or whatever.
وأنك لا تحبينه أو شيء من هذا القبيل
But then you immediately
لكن بمجرد أن تديري رأسك
find a new target.
تبحثين عن هدف جديد
I get it.
أنا أفهم
This is just transferring your affection, right?
هذا نوع من نقل الحب، أليس كذلك؟
But have you thought about...
لكن هل فكرتِ
Ding is our friend.
آه دينغ صديقنا
He's been single his entire life.
إنه أعزب منذ ولادته
After you've healed from your heartbreak,
بعد أن تشفي من جروحك
you'll dump him.
ستتركينه
I feel bad for him already.
أشعر بالأسف من أجله
Jiang Zhihao.
جيانغ تشي هاو
Why are you being so mean?
لماذا أنت غاضب هكذا؟
Am I that kind of person?
هل أنا هذا النوع من الأشخاص؟
If I choose Ding,
إذا اخترت آه دينغ
I'll stay with him properly.
سأكون معه بشكل جيد
OK then.
حسنًا
Great.
رائع
Congratulations.
تهانيّ
Best wishes to you both.
تهانيّ لكما
Why are you scolding me?
لماذا تشتمينني؟
Do you really think I'm that kind of person?
هل تعتقد حقًا أنني هذا النوع من الأشخاص؟
Don't you know you have a history?
ألا تعرفين أن لديك سوابق؟
When you broke up with Gao Bohan in college,
عندما انفصلتِ عن غاو بو هان في الجامعة
you immediately found someone else,
ثم وجدتِ على الفور شخصًا ما
like Du Zhengzhe,
مثل دو تشينغ تشيه
and that smart guy,
وذلك الشخص الذكي جدًا
what's his name...
ما اسمه؟
that top student,
ذلك المتفوق
Zeng Xianzhong.
تسينغ شيان تشونغ
Who?
من؟
You know,
ذلك الشخص
that 'Ciao Ciao' guy.
الذي علمك تشاو تشاو
The one who taught you to say 'Ciao Ciao.'
الذي علمك كيف تقولين تشاو تشاو
That's 'Ciao Ciao.'
ذلك كان تشاو تشاو
Whatever.
من يهتم
How do you even remember his name?
كيف ما زلت تتذكر اسمه؟
How should I know?
كيف لي أن أعرف؟
The past is the past,
الماضي هو الماضي
and now is now.
والحاضر هو الحاضر
Right now,
أنا الآن
all I want is to find
أريد فقط أن أجد
the person who ruined my engagement.
الشخص الذي أفسد خطوبتي
I'm looking for Ding
أبحث عن آه دينغ
because he's the neighborhood chief.
لأنه رئيس الحي
He probably knows a lot of people
ويجب أن يعرف الكثير من الناس
and might help me find some
ربما يمكنه مساعدتي في العثور على بعض
useful security footage.
لقطات المراقبة المفيدة
So you're not after Ding.
إذًا أنتِ لا تريدين التدخل في شؤون آدينغ
Why don't you just die?
لماذا لا تذهب وتموت
But didn't you say
لكن ألم تقولي
you were quite grateful to that person?
أنكِ ممتنة لذلك الشخص
My mom reminded me,
أمي ذكرتني قائلة
look at what this person did.
انظر إلى ما فعله هذا الشخص
Why didn't they say it to our face?
لماذا لا يقول ذلك مباشرة
What were they really up to?
ما هي نواياه الحقيقية
Why did they do this
لماذا يفعل هذا
and embarrass our whole family?
ويجعل عائلتنا في موقف محرج هكذا
Well...
حسنًا...
Did Ding find that person?
هل وجد آدينغ ذلك الشخص
Yes.
نعم وجده
We found some surveillance footage,
وجدنا بعض لقطات المراقبة
but none of them captured this person.
لكنها لم تلتقط صورة لهذا الشخص
Seems pretty clever.
يبدو أنه ذكي جدًا
I must find him
يجب أن أجده
and ask him face to face.
وأواجهه لمعرفة الحقيقة
Why were you so angry just now?
لماذا كنت غاضبًا جدًا قبل قليل
I don't know why I got so angry either.
لا أعرف لماذا كنت غاضبًا هكذا
I really don't know what my dad is thinking.
لا أعرف حقًا ما الذي يفكر فيه والدي
Deng Weikang's small farm project
خطة دينغ ويكانغ للمزارعين الصغار
is clearly full of holes,
مليئة بالثغرات بشكل واضح
yet he's still so proud of it.
ومع ذلك يبدو فخورًا بها
What's the problem?
ما المشكلة
I didn't study marketing.
أنا لست متخصصًا في التسويق
You're so good at it,
أنتِ ماهرة جدًا
can't you teach me?
ألا يمكنك تعليمي
His small farm project
خطته للمزارعين الصغار
fails just on cost control alone.
مجرد التحكم في التكاليف غير كافٍ
Really?
أليس كذلك
Why don't you just tell your dad directly?
لماذا لا تخبرين والدك مباشرة
Wouldn't that prove you're better than Deng Weikang?
ألن يثبت ذلك أنك أفضل من دينغ ويكانغ
My dad only has eyes for him.
والدي لا يرى سواه
If I stand out too much,
إذا برزت كثيرًا
it will only annoy him.
سيراني فقط كمصدر إزعاج
So you're willing to spend your whole life
إذًا أنتِ راضية بأن تقضي حياتك كلها
at Linlin Breakfast,
في مطعم لينلين للإفطار
working under your brother?
كمرؤوسة لأخيك الأصغر
Do you think with my abilities
هل تعتقدين أنه بقدراتي
I should be Deng Weikang's subordinate forever?
يجب أن أبقى مرؤوسة لدينغ ويكانغ طوال حياتي
Tell me.
قولي
You see things clearly as an outsider.
المراقب يرى الأمور بوضوح
Between me and Deng Weikang,
من تعتقدين بيني وبين دينغ ويكانغ
who do you think should take over Linlin Breakfast?
من الأجدر بأن يكون وريث مطعم لينلين للإفطار
I'm not your dad.
أنا لست والدك
Why are you asking me this?
لماذا تسألينني هذا السؤال
We're best friends,
أنا صديقتك المقربة
of course I hope you take over.
بالطبع أتمنى أن ترثي أنتِ المطعم
I almost forgot to wish you a nice trip.
نسيت أن أتمنى لك رحلة سعيدة
Aren't you going
ألن تذهبي بعد يومين
on vacation in a few days?
في إجازة للاستجمام
Yes.
نعم
With your boyfriend?
أنتِ وصديقك
What boyfriend?
أي صديق
My youth and time
شبابي ووقتي
have all been dedicated to your family's Linlin Breakfast.
كلها مكرسة لمطعم لينلين للإفطار الخاص بعائلتكم
Actually,
في الواقع
I think Deng Weijie has a point.
أعتقد أن ما قالته دينغ وي جيه ليس خاطئًا
Listen,
اسمع
small farmers have higher costs,
تكلفة المزارعين الصغار مرتفعة
and their profits are naturally more limited.
والأرباح أصلًا صعبة المنال
So you agree with her?
أنتِ توافقينها هكذا
Of course not.
بالطبع لا
I'm trying to help you find solutions.
أنا أحاول إيجاد حل لك
Do you know why my sister always fails?
هل تعرفين لماذا تفشل أختي دائمًا
Because she's always hesitating and lacks courage.
لأنها دائمًا مترددة وتفتقر إلى الحزم
This plan is just a diversion.
هذه الخطة هي مجرد مناورة
Once the noise dies down,
وبمجرد أن تهدأ الأصوات
we can just cancel the small farmers program.
يمكننا إلغاء مشروع المزارعين الصغار
But... okay.
لكن... حسنًا
Let's not talk about this anymore.
دعنا لا نتحدث عن هذا بعد الآن
I'm tired.
أنا متعب
You should go home and rest too.
عليكِ أيضًا أن تذهبي للراحة مبكرًا
So my thoughts don't matter at all.
إذًا أفكاري ليست مهمة على الإطلاق
You just want to know what Deng Weijie is thinking
أنت فقط تريد أن تعرف ما يدور في ذهن دينغ وي جيه
and if she's planning to go against you.
وما إذا كانت تخطط للانتقام منك
Why are you bringing this up?
لماذا تتحدثين عن هذا
Then why can't we go public?
إذًا لماذا لا يمكننا أن نعلن عن علاقتنا
What are you worried about?
هل لديك أي مخاوف
Here you go again.
ها أنتِ تبدئين من جديد
The truth is,
الحقيقة هي
you're just afraid that Deng Weijie is better than you.
أنت فقط تخشى أن دينغ وي جيه أفضل منك
You're just using me to keep tabs on her.
أنت فقط تستغلني للسيطرة عليها
Xie Jinghan.
شيه جينغ هان
Jinghan.
جينغ هان
Alright, don't be angry.
حسنًا، لا تغضبي
Let's not fight about this every time.
دعينا لا نتشاجر حول هذا الأمر في كل مرة
Don't be upset.
لا تغضبي
Give me a kiss.
قبلة واحدة
Uncle Zhou is actually quite nice.
العم تشو في الواقع شخص طيب
He listened to everything I said
لقد استمع إلى كل ما قلته
and will report to my father later.
وسيجد وقتًا لاحقًا ليخبر والدي
Why don't we meet tonight to discuss it further?
وإلا يمكننا الخروج مساءً لمناقشة الأمر مرة أخرى
Let's go to that place.
لنذهب إلى ذلك المكان
Sure, that works.
بالتأكيد، لا مشكلة
Okay, see you tonight.
حسنًا، أراك في المساء
Bye.
مع السلامة
Weiyu, you're still working overtime?
وي يو، ما زلت تعمل لوقت متأخر
Let's do it tomorrow. They've turned off the AC.
دعها للغد، لقد أغلقوا مكيف الهواء بالفعل
Weiyu.
وي يو
Could you grab the event materials for me?
ساعدني في حمل أغراض الحدث
Sure.
حسنًا
Could that be Xie Jinghan?
لا يمكن أن تكون شيه جينغ هان
This belongs to my brother.
هذا لأخي
Do you have anything on Xie Jinghan?
هل لديك شيء لشيه جينغ هان
In the same place.
نفس المكان
Sister Peng.
الأخت بينغ
I'm going to Japan in a few days.
سأذهب إلى اليابان خلال أيام قليلة
Would you like me to buy something for you?
هل تريدين أن أشتري لكِ شيئًا
You're going to Japan?
ستذهب إلى اليابان
Are you going to visit your mother?
هل ستزور والدتك
Ms. Wang will be so happy to see you.
السيدة وانغ ستكون سعيدة جدًا برؤيتك
I remember she loves pineapple cakes.
أتذكر أنها تحب كعك الأناناس كثيرًا
I'll go buy some right away.
سأذهب لشرائه حالًا
You must bring them to her.
يجب أن تأخذه معك لها
You're going back to Japan?
ستعود إلى اليابان
To visit my mom
لزيارة والدتي
and take care of some business.
وإنجاز بعض الأمور أيضًا
Your mom lives in Japan?
والدتك تعيش في اليابان إذًا
Yes,
نعم
I used to live in Japan with her.
كنت أعيش مع والدتي في اليابان من قبل
So is your mom Japanese?
هل والدتك يابانية إذًا
Do I look like it?
هل أبدو كذلك
Every time I see you,
في كل مرة أراك فيها
I can't stop
لا أتوقف عن
thinking about that moment,
تذكر تلك اللحظة وتلك الثانية
I don't want to
لا أريد الآن أن
say goodbye now.
أقول وداعًا
I won't say goodbye.
لن أقول وداعًا
Thanks for coming today.
شكرًا لحضورك اليوم
Okay, thanks. See you next time.
حسنًا، شكرًا، إلى اللقاء
Zhilu,
جيانغ تشي لو
come straight home after work.
عودي إلى المنزل فور انتهاء العمل
I know.
حسنًا، فهمت
Bye.
مع السلامة
Weiyu,
دينغ وي يو
bring me back a souvenir, okay?
لا تنس أن تحضر لي هدية
Zhilu,
جيانغ تشي لو
I finally found you.
أخيرًا وجدتك
Did you think
هل تظنين
you could hide from me?
أنك تستطيعين الاختباء
I forgot my phone.
نسيت هاتفي
Go get it yourself. My car is coming.
اذهب وأحضره بنفسك، سيارتي ستصل قريبًا
Okay, thanks. Take care.
حسنًا، شكرًا، انتبه لنفسك
Bye.
مع السلامة
Don't think that quitting your job
لا تظني أن استقالتك
means you can get away with
ستجعلك تفلتين من إغوائك لزوجي
seducing my husband.
وكأن شيئًا لم يكن
I've told you a hundred times,
لقد قلت مائة مرة
I didn't seduce your husband.
أنني لم أغوِ زوجك
Then what's this?
إذًا ما هذه الورقة
A loan agreement. What else?
إنها إيصال قرض، ماذا تظنينه
If you weren't
لولا أنك
flirting with him at the office,
تتغنجين في المكتب وتغوينه
would he casually lend you 500,000?
هل كان سيقرضك خمسمائة ألف هكذا ببساطة
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا
Mom, it's nothing.
ماما، لا شيء
I can handle this myself.
يمكنني حل هذا بنفسي
You can handle it?
يمكنك حل هذا بنفسك
You've already handled it your way.
لقد حللتِ الأمر بنفسك بالفعل
Tell me,
قولي بنفسك
when are you going to pay me back?
متى ستردين لي هذا المال
Tomorrow at 10 at the company entrance.
غدًا في العاشرة أسفل مبنى الشركة
I'll bring you the money.
سأحضر المال لك
You better pay up tomorrow.
ستردين المال غدًا، أليس كذلك
Yeah right.
كذب واضح
You think my lady is easy to bully?
هل تظنين أن سيدتي سهلة الاستغلال
She said she'll pay tomorrow.
لقد قالت إنها سترد المال غدًا
What more do you want?
ماذا تريدين أكثر من ذلك
But what if she...
ولكن ماذا لو هي
What if? What do you mean?
ماذا لو؟ أي ماذا لو
You already know she works here.
أنت تعرفين بالفعل أنها تعمل هنا
Don't you?
أليس كذلك
Our place has a minimum charge.
متجرنا لديه حد أدنى للاستهلاك
Pay up.
ادفعي الحساب
Don't look so glum.
لا تعبسي هكذا
There's nothing in this world that can't be solved.
لا توجد مشكلة في هذا العالم لا يمكن حلها
Do you need an advance?
هل تريدين سلفة
It's okay, Mom.
لا بأس يا أمي
I can handle it myself. Thanks.
يمكنني حل هذا بنفسي، شكرًا
Then stop slacking off
إذًا لا تتكاسلي
and help me attend to the customers.
هيا بسرعة لاستقبال الزبائن معي
Zhilu, where are you going so early?
جيانغ تشي لو، إلى أين أنتِ ذاهبة في وقت مبكر هكذا
Nowhere special.
لا مكان محدد
I saved you some breakfast.
تركت لكِ الفطور
Lucky you.
أنتِ محظوظة
I have an upset stomach today,
أنا مصاب بإسهال اليوم
that's why I'm giving it to you.
لذلك أعطيته لكِ
Is it good?
هل هو لذيذ؟
I'll take it with me.
سآخذه معي
Zhilu.
جيانغ تشي لو
Enjoy my breakfast,
عليكِ أن تتناولي فطوري بحماس
stay energetic!
لتكوني مفعمة بالنشاط
I couldn't explain properly yesterday,
لم أستطع التحدث بشكل جيد بالأمس
so today I'm going to make things clear.
لذلك جئت اليوم لأوضح لكِ الأمور
First,
أولاً
I did not seduce your husband.
أنا لم أغوِ زوجكِ
I have zero interest in him.
ليس لدي أي اهتمام به على الإطلاق
Second,
ثانيًا
please stop coming to my workplace
أرجوكِ ألا تأتي إلى مكان عملي مرة أخرى
and harassing me.
لمضايقتي
If you come again, I'll call the police.
إذا أتيتِ مرة أخرى سأبلغ الشرطة
Here's 50,000.
هنا خمسون ألف
I'll pay the rest in installments.
سأسدد الباقي على أقساط
Not a penny less.
لن ينقص فلس واحد
Zhilu, how dare you!
جيانغ تشي لو، كيف تجرؤين
There's only 50,000 in this envelope.
هذا المظروف يحتوي على خمسين ألفًا فقط
It's missing a zero!
ينقص صفر واحد
Are you kidding me?
هل أنتِ مخطئة؟
The IOU doesn't specify
إيصال القرض لا يذكر
that I can't pay in installments,
أنه لا يمكن التقسيط
nor does it set a repayment deadline.
ولا يحدد موعد السداد
This is all I have right now.
هذا كل ما لدي من مال الآن
Take it or leave it.
الأمر متروك لكِ إن أردتِ أخذه أم لا
Zhilu.
جيانغ تشي لو
What?
ماذا؟
You still claim you're not having an affair with my husband?
وتقولين إنه ليس لديكِ علاقة مع زوجي
He just lent you 500,000 like that?
هذه الخمسمائة ألف أقرضها لكِ هكذا
Nothing comes that easy in this world!
أين توجد صفقة جيدة كهذه في العالم؟
Maybe your husband thinks I'm pretty,
ربما يرى زوجكِ أنني جميلة
so he lent me the money.
لذلك أقرضني المال
If you don't pay me back today,
اليوم لم تردي لي المال
I'll sue you for home-wrecking.
سأقاضيكِ بتهمة التدخل في شؤون الأسرة
Zhilu.
جيانغ تشي لو
Ma'am.
أيتها السيدة
Could you please be more polite
هل يمكنكِ التعامل مع صديقتي
to my girlfriend?
بلطف أكثر؟
She's your girlfriend?
هي صديقتك إذًا
Do you know what she's done?
هل تعرف ما فعلته في الماضي؟
Her business is my business.
شؤونها هي شؤوني
I know everything about Zhilu.
أعرف كل شيء عن تشي لو
Then do you know
إذًا هل تعرف
she owes me 500,000?
أنها مدينة لي بخمسمائة ألف؟
Of course I know.
بالطبع أعرف
That's why I'm here to pay for her.
لذلك أنا هنا لأسدد ديونها
Yifei, what are you doing?
نيو يي فاي، ماذا تفعل؟
This is my family's tea house.
هذا متجر الشاي الخاص بعائلتنا
Please don't bother my girlfriend anymore.
أرجوكِ ألا تزعجي صديقتي مرة أخرى
Come to me instead, OK?
ابحثي عني بدلاً منها، حسنًا
There's an ATM outside.
هناك صراف آلي بالخارج
Let's go out now,
دعينا نخرج الآن
and I'll transfer the money to you right away.
سأحول لكِ المال فورًا
Yifei, this isn't your business.
نيو يي فاي، هذا لا يخصك
Sit down.
اجلسي
Come,
تعالي
wait for me.
انتظريني قليلاً
Wait for me!
انتظريني
Wait!
انتظري
Finally resolved.
أخيرًا حُلت المشكلة
That woman was your former supervisor?
تلك المرأة هي مديرتكِ السابقة
She talks too much
تثرثر كثيرًا
and is incredibly mean.
وقاسية للغاية
Why did you come?
كيف أتيت إلى هنا؟
Well, I just...
لا شيء، أنا فقط...
had a meeting with
لدي موعد مع
a supplier.
مورّد
They wanted to buy tea from our family.
وهذا المورّد يريد شراء الشاي من متجرنا
Yifei,
نيو يي فاي
do you know it's obvious when you're lying?
هل تعلم أن كذبك واضح جدًا؟
I'm not lying!
أنا لا أكذب
It's true...
إنها الحقيقة...
I was destined to rescue you this time.
كان مقدرًا لي أن أنقذكِ هذه المرة
How much longer are you going to keep this act up?
إلى متى ستستمر في هذا التمثيل؟
No one's here. Strange, isn't it?
لا يوجد أحد هنا، أليس هذا غريبًا
They changed the location last minute.
تم تغيير المكان في آخر لحظة
How could they change it so suddenly?
كيف يمكن أن يكون التغيير بهذه السرعة
Oh no.
يا للمصيبة
Alright, I should get going.
حسنًا، سأغادر أولًا
The vendor needs to see me.
الشركة المصنعة تريد مقابلتي
I'll head out first.
سأذهب الآن
Let's talk later.
نتحدث لاحقًا
Niu Yifei.
نيو يي فاي
I'll definitely pay you back the money I owe.
سأرد لك المال الذي أدين به بالتأكيد
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك
Bye.
مع السلامة
Welcome.
مرحبًا بك
Hello, miss.
مرحبًا سيدتي
How can I help you?
هل هناك شيء يمكنني مساعدتك به
I'd like to buy coffee as a gift.
أريد شراء قهوة كهدية
But I don't know how to choose.
لكنني لا أعرف كيف أختار
I see.
أهذا صحيح
So his age is...
إذن عمره هو...
About the same as mine.
تقريبًا في مثل عمري
That day was okay.
ذلك اليوم كان على ما يرام
Good thing you told me
من الجيد أنك أخبرتني
what the situation was like.
كيف كان الوضع هناك
You know when I arrived at the scene.
تعرف عندما وصلت إلى هناك
Wait.
انتظر
Okay.
حسنًا
Wait, let me go first.
انتظر، سأذهب أولًا
Then I shouted at her.
ثم صرخت عليها
Made a cool entrance.
بمظهر رائع
She was totally scared.
لقد فزعت تمامًا
She asked me who I was.
سألتني من أنت
I said,
قلت
I'm Zhilu's boyfriend.
أنا صديق تشي لو
Can you get to the point?
هل يمكنك الوصول إلى النقطة المهمة مباشرة
In the end, it was all sorted out.
وفي النهاية تم حل الأمر
Save me.
أنقذني
I'm dead too.
أنا أيضًا انتهيت
You gave me 500,000 then
أعطيتني خمسمائة ألف في ذلك الوقت
and I transferred it right away.
وقمت بتحويلها على الفور
But why did you suddenly have so much money?
لكن لماذا أصبحت ثريًا فجأة هكذا
Can you please focus on the game
هل يمكنك أن تلعب بجدية أولًا
and stop asking so many questions?
ولا تطرح الكثير من الأسئلة
Fine, I'm just curious.
حسنًا، أنا فقط فضولي
When Zhilu got in trouble,
عندما وقعت تشي لو في مشكلة
why didn't you step in to help her yourself?
لماذا لم تتدخل بنفسك لمساعدتها
If Zhilu didn't tell me,
جيانغ تشي لو لم تخبرني
she must have had her reasons.
بالتأكيد لديها أسبابها
Your logic is weird.
منطقك غريب
If Zhilu didn't tell you,
تشي لو لم تخبرك
how did you know?
فكيف عرفت
Your logic is the problem.
منطقك أنت الذي فيه مشكلة
I'm her brother. How could I not know?
أنا أخوها، كيف لا أعرف
Okay, you go first.
حسنًا، اعبر أنت أولًا
Don't jump yet.
لا تقفز الآن
Jump straight in.
اقفز مباشرة
Say thanks to Yifei.
قل شكرًا لـ يي فاي
(Niu Yifei)
نيو يي فاي
Grandma, dinner's ready!
جدتي، الطعام جاهز
Why did you cook so much?
لماذا طبخت كل هذا الطعام
Someone has a birthday today.
اليوم عيد ميلاد شخص ما
A birthday is just one day.
عيد الميلاد يمر في يوم واحد فقط
There are only three of us.
نحن ثلاثة أشخاص فقط في المنزل
What if we can't finish it?
ماذا سنفعل إذا لم نستطع إنهاء كل هذا الطعام
If only your father were here too.
لو كان والدك هنا أيضًا لكان أفضل
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد
Happy birthday, Grandma Hongzhu.
عيد ميلاد سعيد للجدة هونغ تشو
Did Liying ask you to come?
لين لي يينغ هي من دعتك للمجيء
Grandma,
جدتي
I remember your birthday very clearly.
أنا أتذكر عيد ميلادك جيدًا
What does it have to do with Liying?
ما علاقة لين لي يينغ بهذا
Can't I wish you happy birthday?
ألا يمكنني أن أتمنى لك عيد ميلاد سعيد
Quick, make three wishes at once.
هيا، ثلاث أمنيات تتحقق دفعة واحدة
One shouldn't be too greedy in life.
لا يمكن أن نكون طماعين في الحياة
I only have one wish.
لدي أمنية واحدة فقط
Happy birthday.
عيد ميلاد سعيد
Grandma, what did you wish for?
جدتي، ما هي أمنيتك
If I tell you, it won't come true.
إذا قلتها لن تتحقق
She wished for Dad to come home soon.
أليست أن يعود والدي إلى المنزل سريعًا
My wish is...
أمنيتي هي
You,
أنتِ
find yourself a good man
أن تجدي رجلًا طيبًا
and get married soon.
وتتزوجي بسرعة
Me.
أنا
I'm perfectly fine on my own.
أنا بخير وحدي
Why should I rush to find a man and get married?
ما فائدة إيجاد رجل والزواج بسرعة
There's one more dish.
هناك طبق آخر
Don't run away.
لا تهرب
Stay and have dinner with us.
ابق وتناول الطعام معنا لاحقًا
Grandma, not now.
جدتي، ليس الآن
I don't know if Aunt Xueqing welcomes me.
لا أعرف ما إذا كانت العمة شوي تشينغ ترحب بي
You know about her and my mom.
أنت تعرفين علاقتها بوالدتي
I'd better leave now.
من الأفضل أن أذهب الآن
She should be back soon.
يجب أن تعود قريبًا
It's my birthday today. I'm in charge!
اليوم عيد ميلادي، أنا صاحبة القرار
I can invite whoever I want.
يمكنني دعوة من أريد
The garbage truck is here.
لقد وصلت شاحنة القمامة
Let me help you.
دعني أساعدك
This...
هذا...
Thanks for just now.
شكرًا لك للتو
No need to thank me for taking out the trash.
لا داعي للشكر على رمي القمامة
I'm thanking you because Grandma is happy.
أنا أشكر جدتي لأنها سعيدة
There's something.
هناك شيء
Mr. Guang.
العم غوانغ
Dad.
أبي
Lin Liying, get in the car.
لين لي يينغ، اركبي السيارة
Mr. Guang.
العم غوانغ
Ride carefully.
انتبه أثناء القيادة
Dad.
أبي
Lin Guangsheng.
لين غوانغ شنغ
Hurry up.
أسرع
Mr. Guang.
العم غوانغ
Dad.
أبي
Mr. Guang, slow down.
العم غوانغ، قُد ببطء
Be careful.
انتبه
Hurry up.
هيا أسرع
I'm already rushing.
أنا أستعجله بالفعل
Lin Guangsheng.
لين غوانغ شنغ
Is it nice to have your daughter chasing you like this?
هل تظن أنه من الجيد أن تطاردك ابنتك هكذا؟
Lin Liying, hold on tight.
لين لي يينغ، تمسكي جيدًا
We're not going to do anything to you.
نحن لن نفعل لك أي شيء
Look, everyone's faster than you. Guang...
انظر، الجميع أسرع منك... غوانغ...
Wait a moment, safety first.
انتظر، من أجل السلامة
Mr. Guang... Dad.
العم غوانغ... أبي
Mr. Guang is over there.
العم غوانغ هناك
Be careful.
احذر
This is dangerous... Dad.
هذا خطير... أبي
Lin Guangsheng.
لين غوانغ شنغ
Lin Liying.
لين لي يينغ
Or do you want a drink?
أم تريدين أن تشربي الكحول
In broad daylight?
في وضح النهار
Sure.
حسنًا
You'll drink whatever I give you.
تشربين أي شيء أقدمه لك
Why ask such a stupid question?
لماذا تسأل أصلًا
At least you've seen him, right?
على الأقل رأيته، أليس كذلك؟
He's still alive and well in this world.
إنه لا يزال يعيش بخير في هذا العالم
Don't be upset anymore.
لا تنزعجي
We need to go back to have dinner with Grandma later.
علينا العودة لتناول الطعام مع الجدة بعد قليل
So he still remembers Grandma's birthday.
لا يزال يتذكر عيد ميلاد الجدة
Coming back to see her.
ويريد العودة لرؤيتها
Wanting to know how we're doing.
يريد معرفة كيف حالنا
I also want to know how he's doing.
وأنا أيضًا أريد معرفة كيف حاله
Have you ever thought about
هل فكرت
why Mr. Guang left home?
لماذا هرب العم غوانغ من المنزل؟
He has no sense of responsibility.
لأنه عديم المسؤولية
Dumping everything on us.
ترك كل شيء لنا
Leaving debts for the whole family.
وترك الديون للعائلة بأكملها
If that's what you think,
هذا ما تعتقدينه
then do your mom and grandma
فماذا عن والدتك وجدتك
think the same way?
هل يفكرن بنفس الطريقة؟
Would Mr. Guang dare to come back then?
هل سيجرؤ العم غوانغ على العودة إذن؟
I'm not defending him.
أنا لا أدافع عنه
Look,
انظري
sometimes people are just like this.
أحيانًا الناس هكذا
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
You suddenly act on impulse
فجأة تتصرف باندفاع
and make a decision.
وتتخذ قرارًا
But after you've done it,
ولكن بعد أن تفعل ذلك
you might think
قد تفكر
there were other options.
كانت هناك طرق أخرى
But what can you do when it's already done?
لكن ماذا تفعل بعد أن اتخذت القرار؟
There are people like that, right?
هناك أشخاص هكذا، أليس كذلك؟
I'm really not trying to defend him.
أنا حقًا لا أدافع عنه
I'm defending myself.
أنا أدافع عن نفسي
I mean,
أقول
I'm speaking for myself.
أنا أتحدث دفاعًا عن نفسي
It was me.
أنا
What was you?
أنت ماذا؟
On your engagement day,
في يوم خطوبتك
that audio recording
ذلك التسجيل الصوتي
and that secret video,
وتلك الصور المسروقة
I was the one who released them.
أنا من نشرها
I'm running out of time.
لم يكن لدي وقت
What else can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل
You have such poor judgment about people, right?
وأنتِ لديكِ حكم سيء على الناس، أليس كذلك
I can't wait until after you're engaged
لا يمكنني الانتظار حتى تخطبي
to tell you.
ثم أخبرك بعد ذلك
Right?
أليس كذلك
Jiang Zhihao.
جيانغ تشي هاو
Do you think my life isn't ridiculous enough?
هل تعتقد أن حياتي ليست مضحكة بما فيه الكفاية
I don't think that way.
لم أشعر بذلك
Lin Liying.
لين لي يينغ
[Face hit]
ضربة في الوجه
She's pretty hot, right?
جميلة، أليس كذلك
Who?
من
Lin Liying.
لين لي يينغ
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك
I will definitely win her over.
سأفوز بها بالتأكيد
Lin Liying.
لين لي يينغ
Yeah.
نعم
Senior, let me tell you.
أخي الأكبر، دعني أخبرك
We're neighbors.
أنا وهي جيران
She's mean and has no class.
هي شرسة وليس لديها أناقة
She's just a tomboy.
هي مسترجلة
And the key point is...
والأهم من ذلك
Her feet stink.
أقدامها كريهة الرائحة
It's disgusting, you know?
تعرف ذلك الشعور المقزز
Alright, I get it.
حسنًا، أفهم
So give up this idea.
لذا تخلَّ عن هذه الفكرة
You won't be happy with her.
لن تكون سعيدًا معها
Senior.
أخي الأكبر
But when a girl hits this hard...
لكن الفتاة تضرب بقوة كبيرة
does it hurt?
هل يؤلم ذلك
Give up, senior.
استسلم يا أخي الأكبر
[Reveal]
كشف الوجه
Jiang Zhihao.
جيانغ تشي هاو
This is for you.
هذا لك
Why are you suddenly treating me?
لماذا تقدمين لي المشروب فجأة
Then I'll take it back.
إذًا سآخذه
I want it.
أريده
I'm in a good mood.
أنا في مزاج جيد
What happened to you?
ماذا حدث لكِ بالضبط
Say something.
تحدث
I'm eating the pearls.
أنا آكل حبات اللؤلؤ
Here he comes.
ها قد أتى
Senior.
أخي الأكبر
You haven't told him yet.
لم تخبريني بعد
I don't know how to say it.
لا أعرف كيف أقول ذلك
What are you guys trying to tell me?
ماذا تريدون أن تخبروني بالضبط
We're together now.
نحن معًا الآن
You're the first to know.
أنت أول من يعرف
What? You two are together?
ماذا؟ أنتما معًا
When did this happen?
منذ متى وأنتما معًا
Why do you care so much?
لماذا تهتم كثيرًا
No, wait.
لا
Jiang Zhihao, what are you smiling at?
جيانغ تشي هاو، ما الذي تضحك عليه
Congratulations to you both.
مبارك لكما
Let me take a photo for you.
سألتقط لكما صورة
Let's take a picture then. Sure.
دعنا نلتقط صورة، حسنًا
Take a good one.
التقط صورة جيدة
It's our first photo together.
إنها أول صورة لنا
Lin Liying, smile.
لين لي يينغ، ابتسمي
Give me a smile.
ابتسمي
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا
Is this okay?
هل هذا مناسب
Lin Liying, smile more happily.
لين لي يينغ، ابتسمي بسعادة أكثر
How about now?
ماذا عن هذا
I'm just going abroad to study.
أنا فقط ذاهب للدراسة في الخارج
It doesn't mean we're breaking up.
هذا لا يعني أننا انفصلنا
And I'll come back anyway.
وسأعود بالتأكيد
Why did you wait until it was confirmed to tell me?
لماذا أخبرتني فقط بعد أن تأكدت
You know very well
أنتِ تعرفين
how important this school is to me.
كم هذه المدرسة مهمة بالنسبة لي
Something as important as studying abroad,
شيء مهم مثل الدراسة
why are you only telling me now?
لماذا تخبرني الآن فقط
I'm your girlfriend!
أنا صديقتك
I told you as soon as I confirmed it.
أخبرتك فور تأكدي
You can't go.
لا تذهب
After I graduate,
بعد تخرجي
we can go together. Isn't that okay?
يمكننا الذهاب معًا، أليس كذلك جيدًا
By then, my opportunity will be gone.
في ذلك الوقت ستكون فرصة المدرسة قد فاتت
Can't you think about me for once?
هل يمكنك التفكير من أجلي
Making a scene.
تصرف غير معقول
Let me tell you
دعني أخبرك
what making a scene really means.
ما معنى التصرف غير المعقول
This is making a scene. You're making a scene!
هذا هو التصرف غير المعقول، أنتِ تتصرفين بشكل غير معقول
That hurts!
هذا مؤلم
From the very first day we were together,
منذ اليوم الأول الذي كنت معك
I've been making scenes.
وأنا أتصرف بشكل غير معقول
It really hurts!
إنه مؤلم جدًا
Lin Liying.
لين لي يينغ
You don't need to feel so wronged.
في الواقع، لا داعي أن تشعري بهذا الظلم
In this world,
في هذا العالم
there must be someone who loves you.
هناك بالتأكيد شخص يحبك
Maybe he's right beside you.
ربما يكون بجانبك
That person is...
ذلك الشخص هو...
me.
أنا
What are you writing?
ماذا تكتبين
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعلين
Why are you drawing me?
لماذا ترسمني
What do you mean?
ماذا تعنين
Where's Zhihao?
أين تشي هاو
He has a wonderful girlfriend now.
لديه الآن صديقة رائعة بجانبه
I liked you before Gao Bohan did.
أحببتك قبل غاو بو هان
I've liked you for a long time.
أحببتك منذ فترة طويلة
Actually, we've been together for 3 years.
في الواقع، نحن معًا منذ ثلاث سنوات
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبرني
It seems our relationship
يبدو أن أمرنا
is already known by others.
قد عرفه شخص ما بالفعل
You're not even my biological child.
أنت لست ابنًا بيولوجيًا
If I had sent you to an orphanage back then,
لو أرسلناك إلى دار الأيتام في ذلك الوقت
you might have had a better life than now.
ربما كانت حياتك أفضل مما هي عليه الآن
Jiang Zhihao, don't you know how to knock?
جيانغ تشي هاو، ألا تعرف كيف تطرق الباب
If this were following K-drama pacing,
إذا نظرنا إلى هذا بإيقاع المسلسلات الكورية
this would be episode 8,
فهذه يجب أن تكون الحلقة الثامنة الآن
and we'd be kissing in the next moment.
وفي اللحظة التالية سنتبادل القبلة